War Posters Collection
War Posters Collection
- World War II
  - Beat "Firebomb Fritz" – Britain Shall Not Burn - Britain's Fireguard is Britain's Defense, undated; WWII-13; 76cm / 51cm red, white, blue, black (Map-case 53)
    Printer: H.M. Stationary Office by Fosh & Cross Ltd., London
  - Fire Bombs! Guard the Cornfields..., undated; WWII-14; 76cm / 51cm red, white, black (Map-case 53)
    Description:
    Printer: / for H.M. Stationary Office by Johnson, Riddle & Co. Ltd., Penge
  - Put Your Trust in the Navy & Your Money in Saving Certificates, undated; WWII-15; 76cm / 51cm multicolor (Map-case 53)
    Type: Saving Certificates
    Description: Sailors on a battleship
    Artist: The National Savings Committee, London & the Scottish Savings Committee, Edinburg
    Printer: HM Stationary Office by J. Weiner, Ltd., London
  - Wings Over America, Air Corps, US Army, 1939; WWII-16; 2 copies 96cm / 63.5cm multicolor (Map-case 53)
    Description: Eagle flying with U.S. war planes
    Artist: Tom B. Woodburn
  - Be An Aviation Mechanic in the Air Corps / US Army Enlist Now!, undated; WWII-17; 2 copies 96cm / 63.5cm multicolor (Map-case 53)
    Description: Men repairing planes
    Artist: Spezio
  - "Keep 'Em Flying" Is Our Battle Cry! First Class Fighting Men Needed, undated; WWII-18; 2 copies 96cm / 63.5cm multicolor (Map-case 53)
    Description: Army planes flying with & American flag
    Artist: Dan V. Smith & Albro F. Downe
    Condition: some small tears on the edges
  - U.S. Army - Then, Now, Forever, undated; WWII-19; 2 copies 96cm / 63.5cm multicolor (Map-case 53)
    Printer: Spurgeon Tucker, NY
    Condition: Small tears
  - Defend Your Country – Enlist Now in the U.S. Army, undated; WWII-20; 96cm / 63.5cm multicolor (Map-case 53)
    Description: Uncle Sam in 1shirtsleeves with an eagle
  - I Want YOU for the US Army – Enlist Now!, undated; WWII-21; 2 copies 96cm / 63.5cm red, white, blue (Map-case 53)
    Description: Uncle Sam Poster
    Printer: Leslie-Judge Co.
  - Guard Our Shores At Home & Abroad with the Coast Artillery – US Army, undated; WWII-22; 96cm / 63.5cm multicolor (Map-case 53)
    Description: Soldiers outlined the battlefield at war
  - "ACTION!" Men of 18 & 19... Choose Your Combat Branch... / Apply At Any US Army Recruiting & Induction Station, undated; WWII-23; 96cm / 63.5cm multicolor (Map-case 53)
    Description: Various soldiers running by a military plane
    Condition: Tears on the left edge and the bottom
  - US Army Guardian Of The Colors, undated; WWII-24; 2 copies 96cm / 63.5cm multicolor (Map-case 53)
    Description: Soldiers marching with flags & guns
  - Soldiers' Life Make the Regular Army Your Career, 1941; WWII-25; 3 copies 96cm / 63.5cm blue, white, browns (Map-case 53)
    Description: Soldier marching with a gun over his shoulder
  - Vacancies Exist! Enlist Now – US Army, undated; WWII-26; 3 copies 96cm / 63.5cm black, white, red (Map-case 54)
    Description: Black & white photos of war
  - Let's Go! USA Keep 'Em Flying! Uncle Sam needs pilots, undated; WWII-27; 3 copies 96cm / 63.5cm red, white, blue (Map-case 54)
    Description: Planes flying
    Condition: Some small tears on edges
  - U.S. Army – Then, Now, Forever / April 6th – Army Day, undated; WWII-28; 2 copies 96cm / 63.5cm multicolor (Map-case 54)
    Condition: Some small tears
  - Merry Christmas To All – US Army Recruiting Service, undated; WWII-29; 2 copies 96cm / 63.5cm multicolor (Map-case 54)
    Description: Santa Claus holding the world
    Condition: Damage in upper left corners
  - "Keep 'Em Flying" Is Our Battle Cry!, undated; WWII-30; 2 copies 96cm / 63.5cm multicolor (Map-case 54)
    Description: Planes flying with the American Flag
    Printer: U.S. Recruiting & Induction Service
  - "We Shall Win or We Shall Die" / Double Your Shares, 1942; WWII-31; 71cm / 56cm mostly red, white, black (Map-case 54)
    Type: War Bonds & Stamps
    Description: Soldier's face
    Printer: U.S. Government printing office
  - We French workers warn you...defeat means slavery, starvation, death, 1942; WWII-32; 72cm / 99cm multicolor (Map-case 54)
    Type: n/a
    Description: French workers hands in the air
    Artist: Ben Shahn
    Condition: tear on bottom right corner